The Animal Game was created
in Rio de Janeiro in 1892
and was soon declared illegal.
Attempts to suppress it
only made it more widespread.
After the Great Catastrophe,
social chaos took over.
The city changed,
but the game adapted and persisted.
Now as a race between humans,
enslaving the population and
enriching the elite.
One group resists this exploitation,
controlling territory and expanding
the resistance.
Bull runs towards the stairs,
but if he stumbles, it's over.
Horse chose
to follow the alleys and avenues.
It's a bit farther
but we already know his stamina.
Things are heating up
in this decisive heat.
RIO DE JANEIRO
45 YEARS AFTER THE GREAT CATASTROPHE
And here comes the Rooster,
flying along the tracks of Arcos da Lapa.
He won the last two heats,
and wants to be this season's victor.
Come on, Rooster.
First right in 120 meters. Come on.
Bull, cross the street and overtake Horse.
And here's the Bull with no wings,
charging after the Horse.
After the hill, he's moved up a position,
leaving Horse behind.
These animals are running for their lives.
It's dramatic. It's grim.
It's a hit.
But Bull's looking to take the lead.
Take Goat out of the race.
Bull takes Goat out! What a crash.
Will Goat come back from that?
Rooster and Bull are out front.
Neck and neck for first place.
It's a close run.
This final's still up in the air.
And the squad crosses
the Dry Sea of Botafogo
to loop around the Perimeter
and head into the final stretch.
-How's it going?
-Rooster just passed Bull.
He knows he's fast. He prefers
to run alone and avoid confrontation.
-Go, damn you!
-Go!
Whoever bet right,
hold on to that lucky ticket.
If your animal wins,
food and booze are guaranteed.
It helps your family and clears the debts.
There's the Tigress.
She's mad. She's after Horse meat.
The animals are close
to the Perimeter wall.
Now they will cover the 3 kilometers
to the finish line.
No one's crazy enough
to want to take a shortcut.
In there, they don't stand for it.
They are nearly here. Come on.
Any animal that goes in there is hunted,
pursued and massacred.
It's the resistance. They hate us.
Rooster reached the wall first.
Bull, can you see Rooster?
Close in.
-He's the only thing in your way.
-Look who's here. It's Bull.
Take him out.
Use the wall.
Bull makes shredded chicken. Amazing!
Bull takes first place again.
Rooster got run over
and is now in last place.
Things are going badly for him.
Everyone's overtaken you. You are last.
Help me. I need to win.
-Go into the Perimeter.
-The Perimeter?
It's the only way.
The animals are all turning the corner.
If you cut through the Perimeter,
you can still win.
Okay.
What's Rooster going to do?
Not the Perimeter, damn it!
It's no use. He's in there, it's over.
He's in the Perimeter of Death.
The game doesn't fly in there.
Animals are unlucky in there.
I'm in, damn it. Now help me.
That Rooster is screwed.
Any animal that goes in there gets hunted.
Face the Hunter and you'll see.
He can take on any animal.
Who's his collateral?
-This guy.
-He's already lost.
Rooster's collateral is his nephew.
He loses, they take him away.
Another mother left sobbing.
He'll be sent to Hell's Coast.
Sold into slavery,
his soul lost to the devil.
Animal! Animal in the Perimeter!
Run, Rooster! This is too risky.
Turn left down that alley.
He's there!
Rooster! Look, he's there!
Shit, he's in. Go!
The Hunter has seen you.
Go down the alleyway. Run!
No one gets past the Hunter.
That Rooster is screwed!
Take down that drone.
NO SIGNAL
Well, that's it.
The animals are on the homestretch.
The first two win a fortune
and save their collateral.
Bull, Horse, Tigress and Goat running
for a life-changing prize.
Inside the Complex, Bull seems to already
know he will be a three-time champion.
Release the heifers, guys!
This one is Bull's.
Come on! Go!
Go, Bull!
1ST BULL - TIME 48:11:68
2 WINS - 2 LOSSES
BEAST RACE
Are you crazy? That's fucking cowardice!
Fuck! Damn.
It's over, brother. It's over.
I've got two kids. Think of them.
You should have thought of that before.
Are you the one feeding them?
And your collateral,
isn't he worth something?
Bring him, but no messing around!
You won.
Let's go.
Those who bet on Rooster lost,
but the real loser was his collateral.
Too many innocent people have been lost.
Enslaved on Hell's Coast.
Guinea pigs in genetic labs.
The Perimeter will take the game down.
And you are all
going to come down with it.
That's all, folks!
It's the end of the season.
From the 20 that began
to the five finalists,
we saw them fighting it out
on that jungle of a track over four heats.
And Bull wins yet another season.
He won two of four heats and took it all.
Nice, man. Another one.
Let me get your collateral.
They are here.
You guys are mistreated.
What kind of a fucking car is that?
Say hi to your family.
1ST BULL 2ND HORSE
Bull's a three-time champion.
Only Rooster didn't make it.
But that's the game.
I'm Divina, beasties.
The voice of the show for those who bet.
It's illegal, it's cruel,
but that's what people want.
Next season, I'll be on the track.
And things will be better. Okay?
Bet wrong again, Dad?
Yeah.
Soon you will all be betting on me.
Take note. Don't forget.
Hey! Bring the car
to take this animal to the health clinic.
Another one, huh?
Congrats.
You are quite the celebrity, man.
And the chicken?
Who's his collateral?
His nephew.
-Let him go! Come on!
-Mom!
The kid's barely 18,
and he's in the hands of that gang.
No!
And you guys want to do what?
Take him to the health clinic?
Since when is that your problem?
Take your shirt off.
Go on, take it off.
Come on.
We've got an opportunity
and only you two can't see it.
Even more so
with the skin market on the rise.
This right here is worth a bomb.
An animal like this, with a track record.
Look at this, worth a fortune.
-Money for the Perimeter's security.
-Selling human skin.
You are sick, Sinatra.
Don't you have any idea
how shit goes down here?
If you still don't get it, get lost.
Go jump in a lake.
-Little flower, we want the same thing.
-Yeah?
We just disagree on the method.
And don't forget I was born here,
you pacifist.
I'm not a dirty little creature
raised by an animal.
Get moving.
The circus is over. Get moving.
-What's up, Dalva?
-They suspended me.
That bastard, son of a bitch.
I'm going to end up losing
this fucking job, Mano.
I can't take it anymore, really.
We are going to find a way.
-How's Baco?
-The same.
Actually, he's worse.
Drinking more,
spending money we don't have.
-Betting?
-Yes.
-Come on.
-Why do you like this sewer?
Best to stick to the shade.
As an animal hunter,
I'm not exactly Rio's favorite guy.
I wish I had lived back then.
It's pretty.
But they all died
in the Great Catastrophe.
We are lucky to be here.
Lucky? Living with all this crap?
What is it?
The star of the final.
I want an autograph.
Dalva.
You've grown.
The high point of the race
was when you took Rooster out.
Always here to help.
I should be mad, right?
Every day I get a whole bunch of kids
wanting to run.
But a good animal, who can last
7-8 kilometers out there, is hard to find.
Rooster was one,
and he's not the first you've taken out.
And he won't be the last.
What's your plan?
You were always promising.
You could be out there winning.
Run for me,
rather than away from me, damn it.
I'll pay you double.
I'll do it.
The day no animal has to lose someone
as collateral like I did.
Life's no fun without the drama.
I don't give a fuck.
If you want to keep playing
at getting in our way,
rather than getting her
or your stepfather out of poverty,
that's up to you.
But remember I can bring your life
as the Hunter to an end.
Whenever I want.
-The landlord came.
-What did he want, Dad?
-He wants 8000 a week.
-He's going to keep raising it.
Why don't you move to the Perimeter?
You don't get this there.
And live with a bunch of crazy people
who believe they will end the game?
I raised you two by running.
And you lost our mom.
Look here, boy, don't talk
about what you don't understand.
Don't talk about
what you don't understand.
What do you think is going to happen
when I walk into the fucking Perimeter?
Do you think I want to be judged
for running as an animal?
I know how they will look at me.
Exactly. Just the way you are right now.
Ungrateful.
He lived here with Mom.
He will leave only when he's dead.
It seems like that's what he wants.
Fuck, Mano, you should be running.
Helping your family, but no,
you are against the game.
And he's offering you double to play.
How can you think that?
There is a guy in this house
who lost everything because of that game.
But he did something for us.
Unlike you.
Time to go, Mano.
WELCOME TO THE GAME
Congratulations.
You are in the next season.
I thought you were going to stop me.
It seems like you want
to invade my territory.
And you are letting me.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
You have been chosen by the game's board
to enter the hall next season.
Here we have some experienced players
and others who are here
to lose their virginity.
Playing, controlling an animal,
is the privilege of a few,
that makes many people happy.
Every season there are four heats,
with 20 participants.
And now, our collateral,
the unlucky ones from the last season.
Lost, they can be bought or rented,
to be educated, pleasant company.
Your money can pay for pleasure too.
Everyone deserves affection.
You can come up and assess them.
No.
I'll take this one.
You have an owner now.
"You have an owner now."
I think he's going to get rid of me
after this season.
You must be joking.
But you are the one who does it all.
I'm not sophisticated enough.
But you are the one the people like.
And the board will have to recognize that.
Jonas?
Here it is.
Damn! Eagle?
It's fucking awesome. Looks great.
Fucking awesome.
You have been baptized.
Who is going to be your collateral?
I'll have to buy one.
My cousin says there's a channel.
They know
when the person is just an entry ticket.
Do you think I've been training
for more than a year just to lose?
It will work out, okay?
Look at this.
Bull.
What a bike.
If you win, it changes your life.
It's time to change ours.
Let me see if you are really that strong.
-Come here.
-Wait!
-Want me to show you, huh?
-I do.
I like your dedication.
Yeah. I'm counting on you.
You know I can't do that, right?
-But…
-But?
You want to see Leon lose.
Over here, please.
Open your mouth.
Shirt off.
Twist to the right.
Arms up.
Good. Ready for combat. Go ahead.
APPROVED
Come on, little one.
Collateral too.
-All candidates have to be baptized.
-I have been.
-What's your animal?
-Eagle.
Eagle?
Another Eagle.
-So you want to be my Eagle?
-I am your Eagle.
Wow. Let's see.
Okay.
Go on.
Come on!
Fight the cockatoo here.
Get in there, damn it!
Come on! Get up!
Come on! Hit him!
Come on!
Who's your collateral?
Kaká over there.
No, no.
Newbie with bad collateral? Forget it.
Hey, Abu!
What's wrong with his collateral?
-If it were you, that would be fine.
-You are crazy.
-Forget it. But I can bring someone.
-Jerk.
Your boy's good.
Now you just have to do your bit.
Go on.
You made the right decision.
He was born to win.
Mano, listen.
Dalva is collateral.
I'm calling you
because you are my brother.
ANIMALS OUT
Come in.
Have a seat.
Your hand. Finger.
If you try to remove the tracker,
the drug capsule breaks and paralyzes you.
If no one finds you in three hours,
you die. Clear?
That's good, that's good.
I'm going to win.
Show me how you are gonna protect
my sister, you fucker! That's how?
-Stop, Mano!
-What do you think?
That I'm ready to lose my sister, asshole?
My sister will be lost because of you!
Stop! He has to run! Stop, Mano!
Where is it? Show me! Where is it?
Why the fuck did you do this?
You know why.
Abu.
Look who's gracing us with his presence.
She didn't know what she was doing.
No? It didn't seem that way.
But it's too late, right?
We've just got to cheer her boyfriend on.
That kid can't handle it.
You wanted me in the race?
I'm here.
And?
She shouldn't be involved.
Please.
Jonas becomes my collateral
and my sister goes free.
Without her, there's no drama.
Without drama, there's no show.
A good show is
"Brother runs for his sister's life."
That's a proper soap opera.
Get baptized. I want to see
what kind of an animal you are.
Really want to take Bull down?
He's your guy.
Stop!
I can see you are going to be hard work.
-Want to be Lion?
-Of course.
-Why do you think I'm here?
-You are a fucking smart-ass.
That's it. You are my Lion.
What's that sour look on your face?
I was looking at this.
If we manage to expand to Street 3,
we close in on the finish line.
ANIMAL COMPLEX
EXPANSION - PERIMETER
Then it's only a matter of time
before we close in on the Complex.
Mano, what's going on?
Talk to me, baby. It's me.
Dalva became animal collateral.
What are you going to do?
So you are one of those
who thinks being an animal is a bad thing.
The animal is one thing,
the game is another.
Your animal is your nature.
Your beauty.
When you accept the strength
your animal brings…
…the man you were never comes back.
Call him to you.
Internalize that energy.
No one's going to get in your way.
No one.
Be proud of your animal.
Of everything your body can gain from him.
You are Cat.
Always alert.
Always agile.
Luminous.
In the concrete jungle,
the maze is sinister,
and the wildlife fierce.
The first race of season 147
will start shortly.
FIRST RACE
SEASON 147
The players are arriving
and examining their animals,
who are preparing for the start.
This is Divina, keeping you company
over these 8 kilometers
of sweat, blood and blows.
Turn my lion mask into a cat
and give it to your brother.
-I'll ruin your mask.
-You won't. You know what you're doing.
GOOD LUCK
Today's the day!
The first heat
is about giving it your all.
Hey, Lion, listen up.
There's a bunch of people betting on you.
-I got this, sir.
-Fuck.
Crazy. Wild.
Oh, what a good boy.
-What's up, Bear? You chilling?
-All good.
He's sharp.
Hey, Bull. He's Leon's.
I bet cash on you.
Don't let me down, huh?
I want a game.
Hey, Cat.
Ready? Where's your mask?
Listen here, kid. This is serious.
Fuck up and you are out.
You clown.
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Noah's Ark is about to leave.
-Pay attention to the radio. Hey!
-Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, guys! Have a good race!
Come on! Let's go!
Come the fuck on!
Every animal starts somewhere different,
but there's only one finish line.
Only dust will be left behind.
The 20 animals are being left
at their starting points.
After every race, the last five
are eliminated and sink into sadness.
They are out of the season
and lose their collateral.
But this is our nature.
The five who survive until the final,
will fight it out for the trophy
and the cash that comes with it.
Gamblers have studied the animals.
Bets are being taken.
Dreamed of an animal? Place a bet.
From the common man who gambles at the bar
to the millionaire who bets at the casino.
Everyone's watching the race.
I'll tell you what.
Bull has taken the title
in two consecutive seasons.
He was fucked up
when he lost his son as collateral,
but this is his finest moment.
He only gets more violent.
Goat, Tigress and Pig are highly rated.
Lion is a newbie, as is Cat.
A dramatic struggle for these two felines.
If they lose,
it's a brother and a sister who suffer.
Hey, Cat. I'm Nadine, your player.
Time to put your mask on
and win this thing?
-If you can guide me.
-That's what I'm here for.
What kind of crap mask is Cat wearing?
He's trying to act like the Hunter.
That nine lives talk is just a legend,
but if you like to take risks,
this is your animal.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the first heat is here.
Time to unleash the beasts!
Go, Cat.
The maze is narrow.
Everyone's already moving forward.
Those who chose to run on the roofs
have the best view.
Right. Left.
Stop.
Which way now?
-Find a way.
-Overtake Goat.
Bull overtakes and moves up a position.
Cross that slab.
Keep going, keep going.
Starting in the shantytown
is always difficult.
Cat is trying to find a way
through the mess,
bumping heads with everyone.
Go right.
Go, go!
Watch out for Rat!
Fuck, tell me if someone's coming.
Cat is already realizing
there's more to this than meets the eye.
You okay?
-Talk to me, Julinha.
-Goat and Bull are still ahead.
But he swallows his tears and goes looking
for a way out of this maze of alleyways.
Anyone who has swapped rooftops for alleys
is screwed.
Pig, in sixth, has got his blood up.
He runs Cat over and takes fifth place.
They fell into the trap.
Now let's see them get out.
Surround them! Go!
Pig, Lion and Cat
are losing their positions in this cage.
This is fucked up.
They tried to take a shortcut
and now they are all in the same cage.
Anyone not in there chose well.
This is Abu.
He loves watching the circus catch fire.
Close that.
-Do your job, Nadine. Get me out of here.
-Go back to the gate.
I can't. It's all locked.
I found the exit.
Cat's making a break for it.
He started well, but now he's in eighth.
You need to get out
of that maze pronto, bro.
-Get me the fuck out of here!
-I'm trying.
It's my first time.
You are kidding, right?
Don't like it? Do it alone.
-Still there?
-Turn right.
The race is still on.
Lots of lost animals.
Gunk in their eyes, glue on their feet.
Losers eat dust.
-Can you jump 4 meters?
-Why?
Jump now. You will move up two positions.
With that jump,
Cat has proved he's not messing around.
Where did that animal come from?
Bull and Goat are out front.
Tigress in third, on a different route.
After his jump, Cat is moving up again.
He's moving fast,
coming up on the leading group.
Take that Goat out.
Man, Bull got caught.
He's trying to get his bearings.
Time to go Cat hunting.
Go left.
Stay away from Bull.
That Cat better know what he's doing.
There's a reason Bull is known
as the Méier Psychopath.
In the last season,
he put someone in a wheelchair.
He's pure hate.
Go under the overpass
and surprise Cat up ahead.
The leadership remains complicated.
Rabbit in third, on top of the overpass,
with Cat just behind her.
-Cat moves up again.
-Bull is coming.
But look who's here.
Use his speed.
Take that Cat out.
Don't give him what he wants.
Shit!
-Dad!
-That hurts!
Cat's out of the game, and his collateral
goes to the grave with him.
He tried to save his sister and failed.
That's what happens
to anyone screwed on the track.
Animals don't run alone here.
Their families are with them. It's tough.
Cat's losing blood and places,
one after the other.
His race is over.
Cat?
Can you hear me?
Fuck you!
Listen to me, at least once.
Take off your shirt
and stop the bleeding. Now.
-Shut the fuck up!
-We are going to finish this race.
I don't care how.
You have to move up four places
or your collateral is lost. Okay?
Take your shirt off.
I'm not losing this shit.
Cat is back on his feet.
He's fucked up, but it's all or nothing.
Whatever strategy he takes,
he's going to need a miracle.
The leading group is skirting the walls
of the Perimeter.
Listen, our only chance
is crossing the Perimeter.
It's all down to you.
I can't.
I live here.
It's for your sister. You can.
This beat up Cat
has got a suicidal strategy.
He's going to try going
through the Perimeter to move up again.
-Animal!
Animals never come out of there
in one piece.
And he's going through the main gate?
It's Mano!
Who would have thought?
Now you are an animal, you piece of shit!
You are an animal? Asshole!
-Always the way.
-Son of a bitch!
You think we are going to let you through,
son of a bitch?
-Get him!
-Fucking traitor!
You piece of shit!
-Pig!
-Wanker!
-Traitor!
-You are a joke!
-There you go!
-Take that!
Son of a bitch!
Get out of here!
No one touches him!
What the fuck, Marisol?
If you let this animal through--
Shut your mouth, Sinatra!
Have some respect! Shut your mouth!
-Hey, Marisol--
-Respect Mano!
Mano saved you. What the hell?
If that animal gets out of here,
you are fucking done.
You are fucked, you asshole.
Son of a bitch!
Bull has got this sewn up.
Leading this heat,
right at the start of the season.
This is becoming a tradition.
I want to know
who's going to stop that champion Bull.
And it's Bull again!
He's the first to score this season,
and he makes winning look like
a walk in the park.
Shall we go?
You are still playing. I forgot.
See you in the bar.
Goat and Lion are in second and third,
and Bear is in fourth.
-What place am I in?
-Thirteenth.
Cat's still in the running?
He got out of the Perimeter in one piece?
That nine lives shit must be true.
Check out Rabbit leaping by!
Fourteenth. We are still in the game.
This Cat is in danger of falling behind.
The person who comes in 15th
takes the last spot in the next race.
The Cat limps onto the homestretch,
but Horse and Donkey
are galloping up behind him.
Horse overtakes!
-Go, go, go!
-There's one spot left,
and Donkey's giving it his all.
And Cat did it! Fuck!
The newbie comes in 15th
and gets into the next heat.
I thought that guy
was going to die out there. Mental!
He's crazy, but he did it.
Cat takes the last spot.
Even when he falls, he lands on his feet.
It's the end of the first heat, gang.
If you bet right, take the money
and set it aside for next week.
Fuck.
Meow.
I was wrong, Cat.
I expected more of you.
Take care of that. It looks bad.
We've got closer runs than that
ahead of us, gang.
No, no, no, no.
If you like a bit of excitement,
this is the place to be.
I'm Divina.
Not a fan? Don't let the stable door
hit you on your way out.
Until next time, beasties.
Move!
The city is laughing at us!
We lost their respect, Marisol!
-Where the fuck is she? You better talk.
-Stop, stop!
Fucking talk! Where is she?
FUCK YOU!
How could you let an animal
cross the Perimeter?
Listen up. No more being good to animals.
Any animal that crosses the Perimeter
from now on will be skinned and killed.
No more knocking them down
and taking them to the health clinic.
I don't know
if you managed to prove your point,
but I think we got the gist.
Shame it's over.
If you hadn't fucked me over
first time out.
I would rather
not compete with you, Nadine.
But it was your decision.
You became my rival.
Your joints will be renewed
for another two years.
Next week,
we will redo your kidneys and liver.
Make sure you follow the diet.
Excuse me.
It's just a game, Leon.
It's much more than a game.
"A visceral experience, full of lessons
about the human experience."
"The human condition."
Fuck you.
I didn't want to give those people
the satisfaction.
Much less you.
I saw your face.
Cynic.
Is the virtue of love not surrender?
Maybe that's the part of the game
you haven't grasped.
This isn't your season.
Who knows, maybe after I'm in the board,
deciding the game.
I don't need fucking favors from you.
I want to win.
And I haven't lost yet,
you son of a bitch.
It's over, Mano.
-I'm going to the doctors.
-Doctors again?
What for?
Baco lost our mom to this shit.
I'm not losing you.
Lie down.
Once the worst of the pain has passed,
we will go down there.
DRINKING WATER
Good morning.
Can I help you?
I'm looking for the guy
who was Cat in the race.
He runs for me.
Come in.
Thank you.
Who are you?
Your player.
Nadine.
How did you find me?
I convinced Abu
that you had to stay in the game.
What do you want?
To help you.
You guys don't help anyone.
You are here to help yourself.
Of course I want to win.
Everyone does.
Right?
But you are the one with collateral.
What's your plan?
Tell me.
Talking is easy.
It's just a video game, right?
But for us, this shit is real.
-You are going to get my sister off?
-Alone?
But with your help…
You people want to control us,
-even off the track.
-There's no "people."
I'm all you've got.
We are going to run the next race.
Don't talk about my brother!
He's fucked because of us!
Fuck that, Dalva!
He did it because he wanted to.
You are going to help me
get this fucking thing out.
Because I don't want to be lost,
and my brother is in no condition to run.
Understood, Jonas?
Trying to get that thing out
-is practically suicide. Drop this shit!
-Fuck you!
-Open the door, Dalva!
Open the fuck up!
I thought I would be eating alone.
I was trying to stay in the race.
Yeah, your animal. Did you manage it?
We will find out during the next heat.
Don't let it bother you.
This game isn't for you, my love.
You already win through me.
This is the first time I've seen
something make you uncomfortable.
I need you with me, not against me.
You help me stay sane,
but you don't have the luxury
of challenging me.
Bon appétit.
Cheers.
Not long until the next round.
Do you think he'll be able to run?
I'm a doctor, not a seer.
But these are embryonic stem cells.
They regenerate tissue very quickly.
No wonder it costs a fortune.
How are we going to pay for this?
Your player already did.
Now just rest,
and take this every six hours.
Excuse me.
Thanks, Doctor.
Recfi.
-What about it?
-I'm not taking that shit.
Listen, Mano.
Your pride won't heal you.
That drug is from the lab on Hell's Coast.
So what?
Want to send your sister there,
or would you rather run?
All those years on the track,
I've never seen a player help an animal.
And I ran so many years.
-I learned a lot on the track and I can--
-I just need to rest.
Dalva!
What the fuck have you done?
Is this how you greet your friends?
Not going to stand up to speak to me?
Damn.
You are as ugly as ever.
How could she pull shit like that
knowing the risk she was running?
She was desperate.
She didn't think Mano would run again.
This place looks like a fucking hospital.
When did she do it?
Two hours ago.
That's fine, then.
Did your dad tell you we ran together?
-He was good, the bastard.
-She's dying.
But fate is a funny thing.
He ended up in that wheelchair,
and I, a son of a bitch,
was privileged enough to succeed.
And there are people who believe in God.
Do you believe in God, Dalva?
-Are you just going to fuck around?
-Relax.
Relax.
She's just paralyzed.
There's still an hour to save her.
If she takes the antidote.
If I want her to.
Abu.
Save my daughter.
Please.
Because of my history
with your dad and this family,
I'm going to do something I never do.
Spare someone who tried to screw me over.
Take the girl.
Be careful, please.
Didn't you hear the boss?
She stays with me
till the end of the season.
And be thankful.
I should have sent her to Hell's Coast.
She deserves it.
Make the boy take those.
Take this.
-Take it all.
-No, thanks.
-I don't think I can.
-Of course you can, come on.
There are still a few days to go.
You are doing well.
It might not seem like it,
but the game is a partnership.
Animals can't survive without players.
-Hey, give me that.
-But I'm better.
You are not 100%. Here. Juice made by Dad.
Animals can't make it without players.
You must be a unit.
You've got the legs, the muscles.
They are the eyes.
Got it.
It's not enough knowing how to run
and fight, but then losing your head.
They will want to annoy you,
distract you, make you waste time.
That's why you think before you act.
And another thing. Bull.
Bull is strong, but he's predictable.
He's going to want to do the same thing
he did to you last time.
What will it be?
Move over a little and give him a push.
Use his strength to take him down.
Put it on Bear.
Damn.
-A bit rusty?
-I got carried away.
Don't make excuses. You've been
losing to me since we were kids.
It looks pretty from here.
Hell's Coast.
They say there are more than 1000 lost.
And most of them young, like Dalva.
This shit has to end.
It's no use
if only a handful are against it.
People want to dream of a different life,
like Dalva.
No one cares if we lose someone.
I admire you, you know?
You took them on.
But do you really think
you can take down the game?
Wear the mask your sister made for you.
Run for her.
-Stop!
-Gonna hunt me, huh?
Fucking Hunter.
That's enough, damn it!
-That Hunter shouldn't be here!
-And?
Out there, anyone can do what they like.
Kill their mom, put her in the freezer,
whatever. But here…
Here, I'm the one who decides
what can and can't be done.
I want that animal on the track.
If he falls off it, that's it.
Abu, how's Dalva?
Just run. You run.
If you come through alive, we will talk.
Careful. Mind your own business.
Okay, gang.
Heat two is about to begin.
It's the talk of the town.
If you are smart,
you will bet on these beasts.
SECOND RACE
SEASON 147
Hope is a shot that goes down hard
and fires up your heart.
This is the longest heat.
9 kilometers to the finish line.
Take a deep breath. You will need it.
There are 15 left on the track
to race for the jackpot,
but only ten will get into the next heat.
Five will go home,
crying over their defeat.
Pig is highly rated,
Horse slayed during the last race,
Eagle is paying well this time,
but Bull, once again, is the favorite.
And Cat, after qualifying the way he did,
is back.
He hasn't got nine lives, he's got 300.
That being said, if I were him,
I would stay away from Bull.
Good luck, Cat.
I don't believe in luck.
Believe in me. You will need to.
I'm ready.
Ladies and gentlemen,
and now it's…
…time to unleash the beasts!
Go.
And they are off!
Bull takes off in front of Pig.
Go, take that path. Keep going.
That's it.
Horse and Eagle are good.
They are pulling out in front.
-Fuck!
-Wait.
-I can't see you.
-Is it this way?
All I see are trees. I can't see.
Wait, I can't see you.
Today this Cat is more lost
than a needle in a haystack.
Now… right.
Keep heading down. It will be fine.
That's it. Great.
There's a slope 50 meters ahead.
Take Eagle out.
Bear and Bull, the brothers,
running together.
One attacks, the other finishes the job.
Get away from Bear.
That's how they play.
The animals they choose are screwed.
Everyone's in a rush,
and on the verge of leaving the jungle
and reaching the cement of the city.
Desperation, urgency.
This is about survival, my friends.
You are going to see a wall. Jump over.
Rabbit and Tigress are neck and neck,
followed by Bear.
There he is!
Cat jumps the wall and gains ground.
Fuck, you've landed me
right in Bear's path.
Now Bear is looking at Cat.
Don't get into a fight.
Are you playing against me?
Keep going straight.
No, I'm getting away.
Trust me.
You are headed
for an area of shipping containers.
Make the most of the playground.
The animals enter the old port area.
Cat never stops. He's still on the hunt.
Leave Rat. Keep going.
There's no time to waste in here.
It's a mess.
Players that take their eye off the ball
will see their animals fall.
Get up on the container.
Jump.
Cat is looking for an exit.
The flock is flying low.
Eagle, Bull, Goat, Bear.
Here we can't know who's in the lead.
Everyone's looking for the exit.
Go, go, that's it.
This sure is confusing stuff.
-Watch out for Lion!
-Look at Lion!
Showing us yet again, he might be small,
but he's not messing around.
He came in third in his first race,
and he's out for blood now.
Pig's right there.
Fuck, tell me sooner.
Stop complaining. Concentrate.
They are in the game. Get with it.
Keep going and wait for my signal.
Go, go, go. Stop.
Great! Do what I say, we get it right.
First time for everything.
Cat surprises us again.
He's showing his claws.
Put Pig and Bear in the crib
and rocked them to sleep.
Get Lion.
Careful, he's small but strong.
I told you.
Throw him against the wall.
Break him in half.
I have to say,
that's not good for little Lion.
He will fall behind,
if he manages to get up.
And they have finally found the exit
into the Dry Sea.
Now to cross the Dry Sea. You have to fly.
The herd are moving forwards.
They are finally out of the rat's nest
and making progress.
The Dry Sea is a tricky track,
hard going and hard breathing.
There are four more kilometers
to the finish line,
circling the Perimeter's wall.
You are in the city.
Jump the truck and keep going straight.
Bull has taken off,
but Bear is still trying to take Cat down.
Don't let him drag you into a fight.
You are last and you are hurt.
You don't stand a chance.
-You have to go through the Perimeter.
-Not the Perimeter.
If Cat did it, you can too.
There goes Lion, without much of a chance.
He's desperate.
It's his brother who is collateral.
He's headed for the Perimeter.
It's crazy, but it's his only chance.
And it's when animals are desperate
that they screw up.
Don't let him.
-Bear is still on Cat's tail.
-Careful of Pig.
Down!
-Fuck!
-Damn!
What a move!
He tied those suckers in a knot.
Cat's off now.
No one can hold that animal down.
Seriously, bro. Come here!
Get him!
And the leading group is going to
turn the corner and sprint for the finish.
You are ahead. Just keep running.
Go, go.
And they are all neck and neck
on this homestretch.
Rabbit was going to take second,
but she falls.
And Cat is overtaking
like there's no tomorrow,
heading for Bull in first.
The finish line is about fists and dust.
Is Cat going to take this one, guys?
Don't waste time fighting.
It isn't the time for revenge.
It's time to win.
Cat and Bull try to take each other down.
-Stop fighting.
-Go on.
And Bull pushes Cat off the track!
Go, go!
Fourth? You should have been first.
I'm through. Don't complain.
They were messing around
when it counted the most.
And the brothers take first and second.
Goat in third.
Cat, who was leading, takes fourth.
Tigress fifth.
And those were the top five,
who will take a bit of money home.
The rest are still on the track,
sweating it out to qualify.
Ten go onto the semifinal, to fight it out
for five spots in the final.
Abu.
How's Dalva?
Alive.
Relax, I'm taking good care of her.
Come on, come on!
I'm Divina, this is my show.
Until next time, beasties.
He took a shot and he scored. Congrats.
What do you want?
You took my first victory away.
There's no room for an animal like that.
You want a tame little creature?
-I'm through.
-I paid the fucking doctor to save you.
You run for me. Got it?
You have no idea
what it's like outside that room.
While you were drinking your whisky,
my sister was removing the tracker
from her neck with a blunt knife.
You have your reasons to run.
I have mine to play.
The people in that room need to know
I'm playing and I'm winning.
You want your sister back?
Control your hate for the world.
And play with me.
Okay?
How does an animal
become the game manager?
Good question.
I'll tell you.
The best animal in history.
Winner of the most seasons.
I know.
Snake.
She knew.
Snake knows how to find a way.
Right? Look.
Look where the game can get you.
Everything is an opportunity.
Everything.
Now you get to send whoever you like
to Hell's Coast, right?
Without having to risk
any of your little women as collateral.
-What the fuck? Get rid of this brat.
-Stop.
Hey, Mano.
Lucky you didn't hunt down anyone here.
Now you see what it's like.
There's no way out for us.
It's the track or the track.
It's fine to be against it.
Until you need it, right?
To get Dalva out of this shit,
you need partners on the track.
I think he gets
that he's the guys' target.
I'll get you next time, asshole.
THIRD RACE
SEASON 147
What's up, Mano?
Bull's gang is plotting to get you.
Pig, Horse,
and the brothers, Bull and Bear.
And another violent race is over.
The third heat was more violent than ever.
Watch out for that guy.
Shake him off. Go on! Shake him. Go!
And after Bear's fatal fall,
the third heat ends tragically.
Those who are still alive, go forward.
Qualified for the final, we have
Bull, Goat, Pig, Tigress and Cat.
Two of them will take the grand prize
and save their collateral.
Look who's floating on air!
The fucking audience!
Congratulations, gang.
No need to feel sorry for the dead.
Feel sorry for us, who are still here.
I'm sorry about your brother.
But that's the game.
Swallow those tears.
Don't know how to play?
Get off the playground.
How's Dalva, Abu?
I need to speak to her.
He wants to talk to you.
Dal?
You are doing well out there.
I can't wait to have you back.
Baco and I are really missing you.
Just one more race--
He's still got a long way to go.
But he's fine.
He knows I'm looking after you.
What?
When I met you…
you were so raw.
Raw.
And now…
you are going in there,
to fight it out in the final with me.
A present for you.
You are in the final.
Players never meet animals for a beer.
Why did you call me?
I understand
you didn't trust me at the beginning.
I have been in Dalva's place.
I was my brother's collateral.
He ran as Pig. He was good.
He was good.
But one day, he went out,
and didn't come back.
I was 18 when I was lost.
Thank God I didn't end up on Hell's Coast.
A guy bought me,
and now I'm his wife.
I'm not lost anymore, because of him.
And your family?
Leon banned me from seeing them.
You stop seeing the people you love.
My brother died.
I never saw my mom again.
Why didn't you say anything?
I never talk about it.
Looks like rain, right?
Right?
-Look at us.
-I didn't see it coming.
-I said it was going to rain.
-You did?
Why do you play, after all that?
I don't want to be
a part of the game forever.
We can team up against it.
Finish them.
You are in there.
Inside the monster.
I know. I'm trying, in my way.
You only kill the monster
if you cut its head off.
Hey!
Don't stand on ceremony. Relax.
Sit down.
What do you see when you look at me?
In general. What do you see?
Power? Success?
I have a soft heart and no one sees it.
I could have gotten rid of the others
when I met Micaela. But no.
I look after all three.
That's who I am.
I get attached.
I end up taking care of everyone.
A mom asks me to put her son
on the track, I do.
I help.
Shit hits the fan, who fixes it? Abu.
I want to take care of you, Dalva.
So you won't lack anything.
You remind me of your mom, Dalva.
You knew my mom?
I knew her well.
-That's why when I saw you--
-When?
-A long time ago.
Before your brother was born.
But I don't want to pressure you.
That's enough chatting.
Let's have some fun.
Shut up, Abu.
A present.
Take it.
Try it on.
It will look great on you.
-Can I go to the bathroom?
-Sure.
In there.
Idiot.
It's perfect.
That wasn't funny.
I was trying to be good to you.
Mano's going to lose.
You are going to be mine.
Abu--
Abu? What happened, love?
-What's going on?
-It's fine.
-It's nothing. It's fine.
-My God.
Come to Daddy.
I hope you enjoyed your animal.
It's over.
Today might be your last day here.
You should stay here with us.
-And be the fourth wife?
-Perhaps.
Abu wants to take care of you.
I know he can be a bit rude.
But no man gets to where he is
by playing nice, Dalva.
And if I become his favorite, Micaela?
Where does that leave you?
Take the opportunity, darling.
It's easy getting used to the good life.
One day, I want to know
how it works with you guys.
You sleep beside him all night and
don't take the chance to slit his throat.
If I were the fourth wife,
I wouldn't miss my chance.
You think you are clever, right, Dalva?
You and your game-hating brother
who took meds made from the lost.
That's called hypocrisy, darling.
Look here.
When you are back there, girl,
you will remember me.
Mano's never going to win that race.
Abu won't let him.
Ladies and gentlemen, our finalists.
Bull.
Tigress.
Cat.
Goat. And Pig.
Every one of these bodies has a history.
The history of the game, the race.
They are here for the pride
of being a part of this spectacle,
which links the fate
of the rich and poor in this city.
The unfortunate and the privileged
taking risks on the same game.
The assholes wait all season for this.
Get ready for the final!
FINAL RACE
SEASON 147
It's the final. It's the end.
It all comes down to this.
This dry-as-a-bone August's finalists
are ready.
Bull!
The world almost ended,
but the game survived.
-Go!
-Bull!
Bet wrong
and you will be sobbing all summer.
I'll take Cat.
It's been a long road to get here.
7 kilometers stand between
our five animals and the finish line.
And this start looks promising.
Today they start in the city center.
On this brightly lit track,
victory is the goal.
But some of these finalists
could take their final fall.
The stairs will be on your left.
Today is our day. I can feel it.
Run to the end, jump.
There's a door on the left.
I'll wait for you down there.
You are on the 15th floor
and you will take the stairs.
Surprised? We are on the 22nd floor.
We are up the highest.
If we stay up, we will gain ground.
Every animal starts at a different point,
and they are up high, close to the sky.
Might today be Cat's day?
He doesn't seem to be scared of heights.
But it might be Bull's, Tigress's,
Horse's or Goat's day.
Only the first two
will save their collateral.
Time to unleash the beasts!
Go!
And the five finalists are off.
Bull's out in front. He's got one aim.
Getting down to the floor.
Goat, Pig, Cat, Tigress,
are all jumping off precipices,
looking for an exit.
Whoever reaches the street first
will be out in front.
If you jump onto the next building,
it will be quicker getting down, okay?
Bull is hanging over an abyss.
If I were Tigress,
I would have finished the job.
An angry Bull is a dangerous one.
On the second floor, jump.
And you will overtake Tigress.
He's a Bull, not a Frog, but he jumped,
reached the street first,
and Tigress is eating his dust.
Our fauna have reached
the avenues of the city center.
Pig's on his own,
but Cat's on his way, and Bull too.
Things are getting crowded.
The finalists are bunching up,
studying each other,
choosing their moment.
Talk to me.
They are all bunched up.
They are all good.
The bikes are wreaking havoc.
They are there to get in the way,
pile the pressure on, create drama.
That's what people like. What I like.
Get out of there. Get away from Bull.
-Next street, take a left.
-I can't, the bikes are blocking me.
Go!
Watch that Cat.
Those bikes are on top of Cat.
Great! Head left.
He's there, almost on top of Goat.
Tigress comes out of nowhere! Goat down!
And Cat feels the benefit.
The bikes are trying to fuck you over.
That's Abu. Be careful.
Follow him!
Take Cat out!
Pig is on your tail.
Pig is on Bull's tail,
who's always on track.
Left.
And we are back in the bottleneck!
Bull's leading,
this time followed by Pig and Tigress.
Get rid of the bikes, quickly.
We are falling behind.
I can't. They are right on me.
It feels like Cat
is racing the bikes, guys.
Bike on the right.
-Nice!
-Smooth!
He shook the bikes.
I never saw an animal
putting on this kind of a show.
The fans love it.
Speed up. We are well behind.
Find a route.
But this final
is going badly for the feline.
He lost a lot of time on that detour.
Bull tries to pull away
but there are animals on him.
Pig is in the gap.
Look at the Goat! He's back.
He's taken Tigress's place.
She's in trouble.
We have finally got eyes on Cat.
He had disappeared for a minute there.
Come on, Tigress! Come on!
Don't stop, don't stop.
Don't stop. That time will cost you.
Bull's out of control.
I know what I'm doing.
Helping Tigress at this point
in the competition?
That's asking for defeat.
It's practically impossible
for Cat to take this one, my friends.
I think it's over for these two.
They can say goodbye
to their collateral and the prize.
I'm going in. It's our only chance.
Perimeter.
Is this animal going to do
what I think he's going to do?
Didn't he see what happened to Lion?
He went in and never came out.
Cat's crazy. He will do anything to win.
He's trying his luck
in the Perimeter of Death.
Better stay high.
They're watching the streets.
Sinatra, look at this.
Look.
Let's hunt him down.
The Cat's on the wall.
That's it.
Jump over that slab in front of you
and head down.
I can't see you. Get out of there.
I know a shortcut.
Fucking traitor!
-It's over, brother.
-Take that!
-Son of a bitch.
Fucking traitor.
Go, go!
-Let's go, Mano!
-Come on, Tigress!
They are back!
Cat and Tigress have left the Perimeter.
How did he get back in the game?
Amazing!
You will see them coming
out of the tunnel.
The three who circled the Perimeter
are emerging from the tunnel.
Now it's time for the sprint finish.
They are closing in on the finish line.
What a final, guys!
Jump down onto the track.
Cat's in the mix, moving up the ranking.
What a race!
Go.
I have never seen a Bull with a taste
for barbecued Cat before,
but today, we have got just that.
Look at them.
-Bull, Bull, Bull!
-What a final, guys!
And they are facing off
on the homestretch for the last time.
This is familiar ground for Bull.
He's looking to play a final card.
Go, go, go!
Bull is strong, but he's predictable.
He's going to want to do the same thing
he did to you last time.
-Go!
-Get up!
Get up, you bastard!
Cat takes Bull out,
and he's eating dust there,
right before the finish line.
No one can take this one from him.
1ST CAT
TIME 49:58:38
I won.
And the feline takes it, gang!
Cat's first season
and he's humiliated the rest of the fauna.
And that's the end of another season
of the city's most sinister game.
But the machine never stops.
Season 148 is coming, and I'll be there.
I'm Divina, guys.
The voice and face of this thing.
I'm off, beasties.
Who would have thought, huh?
Flying along the track.
Doesn't look like you hate it.
Go on.
You fucking won. Go!
Beginner's luck, Leon.
This won't damage your reputation.
I know it was you who put her in the race.
You are just an animal
with a bit of power. That's all.
Excuse me, the board is waiting.
Senator.
Hi, Cat.
She's not here yet.
So?
The last time she saw you,
you were on the verge of death.
And now you are the season's champion.
You didn't give up on me.
The money I won in there.
So Dalva doesn't try
being collateral again.
Thank you. This…
We will only kill the monster
if we cut his head off.
And the only way to do that is playing.
How are you going to do that?
Alone…
But with your help…
I thought you would want to stay there,
living the life.
Me too.
Come on, I want to see Dad.
Don't be sorry, Abu.
Dalva isn't for you.
Your son wants to play.
CAT
-I missed you.
-Me too.
Are you okay?
Right?
You had a good teacher.
And now?
What will it be?
BEAST RACE